{
    "subject": "resource/Tom_Grosvenor",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/Birmingham_City_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Tom Grosvenor plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8444284796714783,
            "question": "Name a team that Tom Grosvenor has played for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7530030012130737,
            "question": "For which football club does Tom Grosvenor play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7304260730743408,
            "question": "Who is Tom Grosvenor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122870683670044,
            "question": "What sport does Tom Grosvenor play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7110848426818848,
            "question": "What is the name of the team Tom Grosvenor plays for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6733683943748474,
            "question": "What club is Birmingham City F.C.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6417635083198547,
            "question": "Is Birmingham City F.C. a football team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634719729423523,
            "question": "In what sport does Birmingham City F.C. compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6249664425849915,
            "question": "Does Tom Grosvenor play professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5447187423706055,
            "question": "Is Tom Grosvenor a footballer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Grosvenor plays for Birmingham City F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3940_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Tom Grosvenor play professionally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3940_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what sport does Birmingham City F.C. compete?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3940_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Birmingham City F.C. a football team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3940_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3940_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention Tom Grosvenor playing as an inside right and taking part in more than 100 games for Birmingham City Football Club in the Football League First Division. This supports the statement that Tom Grosvenor plays for Birmingham City F.C."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Tom Grosvenor plays for Birmingham City F.C.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention his time with Birmingham City Football Club, indicating he did indeed play for them."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}